<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our Services on Fabtekk Engineering</title>
    <link>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our Services on Fabtekk Engineering</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:38:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Condition Reports</title>
      <link>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/condition-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/condition-reports/</guid>
      <description>A site visit, inspection and comprehensive report on specified equipment within the organisation. The report provides a professional, impartial and stand- alone document for the customers use, based on the expert opinion of the directors on the status and condition of the specified equipment.
The aim of the condition report is to identify issues, but also present solutions, in this regard, the report makes use of two systems to provide the best and most comprehensive advice possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Refurbishments</title>
      <link>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/refurbishments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/refurbishments/</guid>
      <description>We offer a refurbishment service across all equipment; this provides customers a viable cost-effective option at a fraction of the price of acquiring new equipment.
In the first instance, an evaluation will be conducted to assess the current operational condition and the expectancy for the machine’s performance. An assessment of what can be realistically achieved will be discussed with the customer. Once the project is agreed, a careful and methodical process of dismantling the machine occurs, and the refurbishment process begins to restore the equipment; offering new life to tired machinery, with the aim of bringing it back to a reliable and expected factory standard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installations/Decommissioning</title>
      <link>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/installations-and-decommissioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/installations-and-decommissioning/</guid>
      <description>Installations We offer an installation service for any manufacturing equipment, installing new or relocating existing equipment. We also provide advice on the layout to maximise production and aid with planning if required.
Decommissioning A sensitive and effective de-commissioning service, dismantling existing machinery, with removal from your premises, including the transportation of the machinery to a site of your choice or disposal if preferred.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shift Cover</title>
      <link>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/shift-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/shift-cover/</guid>
      <description>Experienced engineering professionals can be provided to temporarily support you, providing shift cover when your permanent staff are on planned or unexpected absences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oven Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/oven-cleaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/oven-cleaning/</guid>
      <description>Oven Cleaning, General Inspection and Condition Report Our engineers provide a concentrated clean of the oven, removing debris that presents a fire risk and impacts on output of the machine. Whilst undertaking the cleaning process we also do a visual oven inspection of both the oven chamber and the external oven walls and roof.
The internal inspection will highlight any findings that can pose an imminent risk of oven failure and identify those that present a medium risk, which can be rectified before a failure occurs, with remedial works and a planned shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Call Out</title>
      <link>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/emergency-call-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/emergency-call-out/</guid>
      <description>We offer a 24 hour emergency call out service in the event of machine failure. Our strength lies in our team and in our ability to provide the right skills at the right time to support when the unexpected occurs. Best endeavours are at the heart of this service and our engineers will aim to get the machine back in operation soonest, acutely aware of the implications and impact to your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preventative Maintenance</title>
      <link>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/preventative-maintenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/preventative-maintenance/</guid>
      <description>Our engineering team is dedicated to ensuring the best possible performance of your machinery Through helping prolong its life expectancy by undertaking planned preventative maintenance schedules and rectifying problems that are uncovered.
Identifying and rectifying issues before they present themselves as breakdowns is a more cost-effective operating model than calling on service professionals in an emergency situation; unplanned downtime could jeopardise orders and reputation with customers.
A maintenance program allows organisations to budget accurately for parts and non-productive down time (budgeting for emergencies can be tricky), thus providing a level of control in the operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabrication and Spares</title>
      <link>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/fabrication-and-spares/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/fabrication-and-spares/</guid>
      <description>We offer high quality mechanical replacement parts and accessories This is to help ensure the long and productive life of all important pieces of equipment.
To this end we can either provide genuine manufacturer parts or fabricate reengineered components at a competitive price.
(include some images of parts and stuff here, possibly with links to the corresponding projects they were from on the portfolio page).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Divider servicing</title>
      <link>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/divider-servicing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adaptableyam-fabtekk.github.io/services/divider-servicing/</guid>
      <description>Dough dividers are used in bakeries to divide high volumes of dough into quantities of equal size and weight. Reliability of the Divider could be impacted if not well-maintained and there could be a variation in weights and measures that increases wastage, impacting profitability and potentially service delivery to customers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
